Heiko Oberman Papers 1949-2016 (bulk 1985-2001)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Publications, 1958-2005; Series VIII
  - Publications, HAO (continued), 1982-1985 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Publications, HAO, 1986-1989 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Publications, HAO, 1990-1995 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Publications, HAO (continued), 1990-1995 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Publications, HAO (continued), 1990-1995 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Publications, HAO, 1996-2003 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Publications, HAO (continued), 1996-2003 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Publications, HAO, newspaper, 1962-1965 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Publications, HAO, newspaper, 1966-1968 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Publications, HAO, newspaper, 1974-1976 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Publications, HAO, newspaper, 1980 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Publications, HAO, newspaper, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Publications, HAO, newspaper, 1986 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Publications, HAO, newspaper, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Publications, other authors, Carl Friederich von Baden, copy of 1783 document (possibly outlawing serfdom), undated (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Publications, other authors, signed by author with note to HAO, 1988-2001 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Publications, other authors, 1981-2001 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Publications, other authors, 1986-2005 (Box 27, Folder 25)
- Media (floppies, CDs), circa 1980-2000; Series IX
  - Media (floppies, CDs), circa 1980-2000 (Box 28)
- Audio Visual Materials, circa 1960-2000; Series X
  - Audio Visual Materials, circa 1960-2000 (Box 29)